media247.co.uk 2013-04-20

# Privacy Policy | Media247 UK

Last updated: January 2012

Media 247 has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices applicable to any personal information, which is given by You to Us (“User Information”) via the web site located at www.media247.co.uk (“Site”).

“You” shall mean you, the user of the site, “Media 247/We” shall mean Media 247 and its associated members and the “Media 247″ shall have the meaning as set out above.

**Information About All Media 247 Visitors**  
In general, our service automatically gathers certain “ratings” information when a visitor comes to Media 247. We only use such data in the aggregate.

This collective data helps us determine how much our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site to assure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. For example, Media 247 uses a technology nicknamed “cookies” that tells us how and when pages in our site are visited, and by how many people.

Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your screen name or e-mail address is. We also may provide statistical “ratings” information, never information about you personally, to our Media 247 partners about how our members, collectively, use Media 247.

We do this so they too can understand how much people use their areas and our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible Web experience as well.

**Information About You**  
Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service.

We will need certain information — such as name and email address – in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested.

Additionally, we may provide you with an opportunity to be listed in our weekly Media 247 newsletter – these listings are also optional and you can make changes to or eliminate this information when you want to.

**Disclosure**  
We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to Media 247 or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. But as we mention above, we may share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical “ratings” information about the use of Media 247.

**Media 247 Privacy Policy Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy for Media 247, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.
